EDEN

DAYAN

CONTACT INFO

E-mail Eden8557021@gmail.com

Phone 052-621-1386 Address Holon, Israel

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/eden-dayan-97780616a

GitHub https://github.com/edend85

ABOUT ME

My hands-on experience with networking systems and practical software engineering degree give me a solid foundation in our technological world. My experience has proved I can deal with high-pressure, challenging environments, and my optimistic approach allows me to excel as a team player.

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL SUPPORTER

2018-NOW

Ness Technology | Bank Hapoalim

- Support investment houses and private business clients.
- Experience with: CA Service Desk, Network Access Control (NAC), Cyber Ark vaults, Citrix Workspace program

TEAM-LEADER

2016-2017

Intelligence Corp | IDF

• I served as a technician and as a technical supporter of security systems in the operational environment while managing a team of soldiers.

EDUCATION

Practical Software Engineer

2021- NOW

Shenkar College of Engineering, Design and Art

- Theoretical and practical knowledge in numerous software engineering and computer science disciplines. Including OOP, data structures, algorithms and others.
- Current grade Average: 92.8
- Awarded an Honor roll for my first year.

PROJECTS

Final programming project

2023

Shenkar College of Engineering, Design, and Art

- "SmokEye" is an application that allows users to report smoking violations in public areas, gain information about smoking laws, and find places designated for smokers. It also allows researchers to collect smoking-related data collected from the app.
- Developed for Dr. Yael Bar-Zeev, Israeli Ministry of Health
- We utilized different technologies; reactJS, react native, node.js, MongoDB and GitHub.

SKILLS

● ● ○ C Sharp, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, React Native

● O O Node.js, mongoDB, SQL,git,python

Languages

• Hebrew (native)

• English (proficient)